export const math_coaching_economics = [
    {
        choices: ["sinking fund method", "declining balance method", "straight method", "sum of the years digit method"],
        correctAnswer: "sinking fund method",
        question: "The method of depreciation which assumes that a sinking fund is established in which funds will accumulate for replacement.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["post inventory", "perpetual inventory", "physical inventory", "partial inventory"],
        correctAnswer: "perpetual inventory",
        question: "A type of inventory of materials which consists of the preparation of inventory cards and their being kept up to date for each type of equipment or materials used or issued and for the products completed or in the process of manufacture.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["present worth method", "equity point", "replacement point", "break-even point"],
        correctAnswer: "break-even point",
        question: "The quantity of production at which the income is equal to total cost",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["total liabilities", "current liabilities", "future liabilities", "fixed liabilities"],
        correctAnswer: "current liabilities",
        question: "Liabilities which mature within a short time, usually a year.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["capital recovery", "expected yield", "economic return", "earning value"],
        correctAnswer: "economic return",
        question: "The profit derived from a project or business enterprise without consideration of obligations to financial contributors or claims of other based on profit.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["market value", "book value", "fair value", "use value"],
        correctAnswer: "fair value",
        question: "The value is usually determined by a disinterested third party in order to establish a price that is fair to both seller and buyer.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["compound interest", "simple interest", "ordinary interest", "discounted interest"],
        correctAnswer: "simple interest",
        question: "An interest calculated using the principal only, ignoring any interest that had been acquired in preceding periods.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["absolute seniority", "definite seniority", "department seniority", "synthetic seniority"],
        correctAnswer: "synthetic seniority",
        question: "War veterans, even though not company employees before the war, given credit for their military service",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["accounting records", "income tax return", "balance sheet", "ledger"],
        correctAnswer: "balance sheet",
        question: "A financial summary showing the relationship among assets, liabilities, and ownership in the corporation on a specific date.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Industrial union", "Firemans union", "Workers clan", "Senior group"],
        correctAnswer: "Industrial union",
        question: "This is an association of all employees of an industry regardless of the type of work or skill possessed by the individual.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Liabilities", "Quit claim", "Equities", "Obligations"],
        correctAnswer: "Liabilities",
        question: "Debts or claims of anyone other than the owners of the property upon the assets of the company. It consists of all the obligations of the company to other persons in the form of money, other assets or services to be paid now or in the future.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["rate of interest", "rate of return", "effective rate of interest", "rate of discount"],
        correctAnswer: "rate of discount",
        question: "The discounte on one unit of principal for one unit of time",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["credit entry", "debit entry", "journal", "transaction record"],
        correctAnswer: "journal",
        question: "An accounting book where the original record of a transactions is ordinarily recorded.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Return", "Share stock", "Dividend", "Par value"],
        correctAnswer: "Dividend",
        question: "The amount of company&amp;amp;#39;s profit that the board of directors of the corporation decides to distribute to ordinary shareholders.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["amortization", "depreciation", "annual cost", "annuity"],
        correctAnswer: "annuity",
        question: "A series of equal payments occuring at equal periods of time.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["goodwill value", "franchise value", "book value", "going value"],
        correctAnswer: "going value",
        question: "An intangible value which an actually operating concern has due to its operation",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["current ratio", "acid test ratio", "rate of return", "debt ratio"],
        correctAnswer: "acid test ratio",
        question: "The ratio of the quick assets to the current liabilities is",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["declining balance method", "sum of the years digit method", "sinking fund method", "straight line method"],
        correctAnswer: "declining balance method",
        question: "The method of depreciation sometimes called the constant percentage method of the Matheson formula, it is assumed that the annual cost of depreciation is an fixed percentage of the salvage value at the beginning of the year.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["currency devaluation", "currency depreciation", "currency appreciation", "currency float"],
        correctAnswer: "currency devaluation",
        question: "The deliberate lowering of the price of nations currency in terms of the accepted standard.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["franchise value", "goodwill value", "book value", "going value"],
        correctAnswer: "goodwill value",
        question: "The element of value which a business has earned through the favorable consideration and patronage of its customers arising from its well-known and well conducted policies and operation",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Tangible factors", "Stock", "Equity", "Intangible factors"],
        correctAnswer: "Equity",
        question: "Which of the following is the claim of anyone to ownership?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Mortgage bonds", "Coupon bonds", "Collateral trust bonds", "Debenture bonds"],
        correctAnswer: "Coupon bonds",
        question: "Bonds which are attached coupons indicating the interest due and the date when such interest is to be paid.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["market", "demand", "utility", "supply"],
        correctAnswer: "demand",
        question: "The quantity of a certain commodity that is bought a a certain price at a given time and place.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["stock", "utility", "commodity", "necessity"],
        correctAnswer: "commodity",
        question: "Any particular raw material or primary product such as cloth, flour, coffee,..., etc is called",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["elastic demand", "unitary elasticity", "inelastic demand", "perfect elasticity"],
        correctAnswer: "inelastic demand",
        question: "Occurs when a decrease in the selling price produces a less than proportionate increase in sales.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["cost push", "recession", "demand pull", "stagnation"],
        correctAnswer: "recession",
        question: "A situation in which the average price level rises because suppliers have taken the initiative to raise prices above the equilibrium level or if they seek higher profits margins:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["labor cost", "expenses", "investment", "construction cost"],
        correctAnswer: "expenses",
        question: "Cost of things that are neither nor material.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Liquid assets", "Fixed assets", "Current assets", "Prepaid expense"],
        correctAnswer: "Prepaid expense",
        question: "The assets in the form of money paid for certain materials not yet delivered or services not yet rendered to the company.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["sanctions to grievance", "arbitration of grievance", "solution to grievance", "answer to grievance"],
        correctAnswer: "arbitration of grievance",
        question: "This is the final step after a grievance has gone through the varios channels of shop steward",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["going concern value", "goodwill", "fair value", "networth"],
        correctAnswer: "going concern value",
        question: "The difference between the value of the property as it stands ready for operation and its value as it would stand at completion of consturciton as an inert assembly of physical parts.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["5", "10", "15", "3"],
        correctAnswer: "10",
        question: "The minimum number of incorporators in order that a corporation be organized is",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["deflation", "depletion", "inlation", "stock watering"],
        correctAnswer: "stock watering",
        question: "If an increase in the capital stock is made when actually no additional value has been paid either in cash or in money&amp;amp;#39;s worth",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["discount", "advance interest", "effective rte of interest", "expenses"],
        correctAnswer: "discount",
        question: "An interest deducted in advance is",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["open wide seniority", "absolute seniority", "department seniority", "synthetic seniority"],
        correctAnswer: "department seniority",
        question: "Only length of service in a particular department is considered in computing seniority",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["property life", "physical life", "investment life", "economic life"],
        correctAnswer: "economic life",
        question: "The length of time during which the property maybe operated at a profit is",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["development cost", "marginal cost", "differential cost", "variable cost"],
        correctAnswer: "differential cost",
        question: "The costs which arise at the result of a change in operations or policy or it is the ratio of a small increment of output.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["deficits", "total losses", "isoquant", "total profits"],
        correctAnswer: "total profits",
        question: "A positive difference between the firms total receipts or revenues and the total costs is known as",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["development cost", "original cost", "promotion cost", "construction cost"],
        correctAnswer: "development cost",
        question: "The sum of all the costs incurred by the originators of the project up to the time that the project up to the time that the project is accepted by the promoters of the project.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["memorandum", "barter", "bond", "contract"],
        correctAnswer: "contract",
        question: "A legally agreement or promise to exchange goods or services.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["ticket", "Bill of Lading", "contract to ship", "crate bill"],
        correctAnswer: "Bill of Lading",
        question: "A written acknowledgement by a carrier that he has received the goods for shipment",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["ordinary annuity", "perpetuity", "deferred annuity", "annuity due"],
        correctAnswer: "perpetuity",
        question: "An annuity in which the payments continue indefinitely is",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["physical inventory", "perpetual inventory", "on-date inventory", "perfect inventory"],
        correctAnswer: "physical inventory",
        question: "A type of inventory of materials which consist of the actual counting or determination of the actual quantity of materials on hands of a given date.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Return", "Goodwill", "Debenture", "Capital gain"],
        correctAnswer: "Capital gain",
        question: "It is the profit obtained by selling stocks at a higher price than its original purchase price.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["equity capital", "borrowed funds", "invested capital", "onwership funds"],
        correctAnswer: "borrowed funds",
        question: "Funds supplied by others on which a fixed rate of interest must be paid and the debt must be repaid at a specific time.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["personal check", "company check", "certified check", "managers check"],
        correctAnswer: "certified check",
        question: "A check drawn from a depositor against his account which the bank has marked certified.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["open seniority", "plant wide seniority", "notation seniority", "limited seniority"],
        correctAnswer: "plant wide seniority",
        question: "Length of service with the company regardless of the division or department is the yardstick employed.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Cooperative", "Corporation", "Union", "Partnership"],
        correctAnswer: "Cooperative",
        question: "A form of business firm which is owned and run by a group of individuals for their mutual benefit",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["closed shop", "nonunion shop", "exclusive shop", "open shop"],
        correctAnswer: "open shop",
        question: "Normally these are phrases indicating that a plant has only nonunion members as employees or where the union is not recognized as such",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Collateral trust bonds", "Mortgage bonds", "Debenture bonds", "Coupon bonds"],
        correctAnswer: "Mortgage bonds",
        question: "Bonds whos security behind them is a mortgage on certain specified assets of the corporation.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["oligopoly", "oligopsony", "duopoly", "perfect competition"],
        correctAnswer: "oligopoly",
        question: "A condition where only few individuals produce a certain product that action of one will lead to almost the same action by the other.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Perpetuity", "Deferred annuity", "Annuity due", "Ordinary annuity"],
        correctAnswer: "Annuity due",
        question: "A type of annuity where the payments are made at the start of each period beginning from the first period.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["peso", "money", "gold", "dollar"],
        correctAnswer: "money",
        question: "Acts as medium of exchange, as a common denominator of values",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["liquidated damages", "delayed payments", "unliquidated damages", "advance damages"],
        correctAnswer: "liquidated damages",
        question: "Means the sum agreed upon in advance by the parties as compensation for a breach",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["price optimization", "price war", "price discrimination", "price manipulation"],
        correctAnswer: "price discrimination",
        question: "The act of charging two or more buyers or sellers different prices for the same product where the elasticities of suppy or demand at each price level differ among the markets;",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["physical depreciation", "depletion", "normal depreciation", "functional depreciation"],
        correctAnswer: "functional depreciation",
        question: "The type of depreciation due to the lessening in the demand for the function which property was designed to render",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["promises", "agreement", "promissory note", "contract"],
        correctAnswer: "promissory note",
        question: "A written promies to pay on demand or at a fixed and determined future time",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["pot pay", "clothing allowance", "travel pay", "portal-to-portal pay"],
        correctAnswer: "portal-to-portal pay",
        question: "A term used to describe payment of an employee for time spent on the property of an employer though not actually working at the job or time spent changing clothes to get ready for work or time spent traveling from the plant entrance to the place of work.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["non-conventional cash flows", "evaluation over different periods", "mutually exclusive projects", "difference in the magnitude of the projects"],
        correctAnswer: "evaluation over different periods",
        question: "When using net present worth calculation to compare two objects, which of the following could invalidate the calculations.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["sinking fund", "discrete compounding", "continuous compounding", "discounting"],
        correctAnswer: "discrete compounding",
        question: "When the interest is compounded at the end of each period of some finite length, like a month, quarter or year, this type of compounded payment is categorized as",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Intangible factors", "Tangible factors", "Stock", "Equity"],
        correctAnswer: "Intangible factors",
        question: "Factors which are impossible or difficult to express in terms of monitary value.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["fair value", "goodwill value", "market value", "book value"],
        correctAnswer: "fair value",
        question: "The value which a disinterested party, different from the buyer or seller, will determine in order to establish a price that is acceptable to both the buyer and the seller.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["acid test ratio", "current ratio", "rate of return", "quick ratio"],
        correctAnswer: "rate of return",
        question: "The ratio of the annual net profit to the amount of capital invested.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["producer goods", "none of these", "substitute goods", "coplementary goods"],
        correctAnswer: "substitute goods",
        question: "The type of goods in which the increase of consumption of one decreases the marginal rate of substitution for the other for money and its characterized by the leftward shift of the demand curves as the price is increased:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["receivable turnover", "asset turnover", "current ratio", "inventory turnover"],
        correctAnswer: "inventory turnover",
        question: "It is defined as the cost of materials used during the year divided by the average investment in materials.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["capital expenditure", "capital loss", "deficit", "depletion"],
        correctAnswer: "capital loss",
        question: "The reduction in the money value of a capital asset is called",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["credit", "purchasing power", "wealth", "defit"],
        correctAnswer: "credit",
        question: "The power or ability to obtain goods and services with a promise to pay at a definite future time.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["sinking fund method", "declining balance", "sum of the digit method", "straight line method"],
        correctAnswer: "straight line method",
        question: "The method of depreciation which assumes that the loss in value is directly proportional to the age of the property",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["nominal rate of interest", "simple interest", "effective rate of interest", "compound interest"],
        correctAnswer: "nominal rate of interest",
        question: "It specifies the rate of interest and a number of interest periods in one year.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["construction cost", "production cost", "promotion cost", "prime cost"],
        correctAnswer: "production cost",
        question: "The sum of direct material cost, direct labor cost and overhead cost",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Joint bonds", "Debenture bonds", "Collateral trust bonds", "Mortgage bonds"],
        correctAnswer: "Joint bonds",
        question: "Bonds issued by two or more corporations and are guaranteed jointly by them.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["deferred annuity", "amortization", "perpetuity", "annuity"],
        correctAnswer: "amortization",
        question: "Any method of repaying a debt, the principal and interest included usually by a series of equal payments at periodic intervals of time.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Acid test ratio", "Equity ratio", "Dividend yield", "Price - earning ratio"],
        correctAnswer: "Price - earning ratio",
        question: "The index which indictes wheter price of stock is compatible with earnings.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Law of demand", "Law of supply and demand", "Law of diminishing return", "Law of supply"],
        correctAnswer: "Law of diminishing return",
        question: "When the use of one factors of production is limited, either in increasing cost or by absolute quantity, a point will be reached beyond which an increase in the variable factors will result in a less than proportionate increase in output.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["use of callable bonds", "use of sinking fund", "either A or C", "none of these"],
        correctAnswer: "use of callable bonds",
        question: "Certificate of indebtness of a corporation guaranteed by a mortgage on certain assets may be retired by",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["individual ownership", "sole proprietorship", "corporation", "partnership"],
        correctAnswer: "corporation",
        question: "A distinct legal entity, sepearte from the individuals who own it and which can engage in almost any type of of business transaction in which a real person could occupy himself or herself",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["useful life", "physical life", "normal life", "economic life"],
        correctAnswer: "physical life",
        question: "The length of time during which it is capable of performing the function for which it was designed and manufactured",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["gross profit", "net income", "differential cost", "discount"],
        correctAnswer: "gross profit",
        question: "The difference between sales revenue and the cost of goods sold",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["deferred loan", "fixed-rate loan", "balloon mortgage", "equity loan"],
        correctAnswer: "balloon mortgage",
        question: "A loan which is not fully paid off by the last installment payment.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["differential cost", "increment cost", "marginal cost", "overhead cost"],
        correctAnswer: "marginal cost",
        question: "The additional cost producing one more unit",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["sealed bond", "collateral bond", "corporation bond", "coupon bond"],
        correctAnswer: "corporation bond",
        question: "A written contract, under seal, whereby a corporation binds itself to pay a specific sum of money to the owner of the bond.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["dividend per share on common stock", "book value per share of common stock", "earnings per share on common stock", "return on common stockholder&amp;amp;#39;s equity"],
        correctAnswer: "book value per share of common stock",
        question: "The index which indicates the recorded value of net assets for each share of common stock.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["inelastic demand", "unitary elasticity", "elastic demand", "perfect elasticity"],
        correctAnswer: "elastic demand",
        question: "Occurs when a decrease in the spelling price results in a greater than proportionate increase in sales.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Goodwill value", "Book value", "Fair value", "Market value"],
        correctAnswer: "Market value",
        question: "The amount of a property in which a willing buyer will pay to a willing seller for the property when neither one is under the compulsion to buy or sell.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Equity", "Tangible factors", "Intangible factors", "Stock"],
        correctAnswer: "Stock",
        question: "Which of the following represents ownership in a corporation?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["law of marginal utility", "law of diminishing return", "none of these", "law of diminishing utility"],
        correctAnswer: "law of diminishing utility",
        question: "An increase in the quantity of any good consumed or acquired by an individual will decrease the amount of satisfaction derived from that good. This is known as",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["scrap cost", "sunk cost", "discount", "loss"],
        correctAnswer: "sunk cost",
        question: "It represents money which has been spent or capital which has been invested and which cannot be recovered due to certain reasons, or it may be defined as the unrecovered balance remaining if the net income received is less than the amount of capital invested.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["compound interest", "simple interest", "nominal interest", "discounted interest"],
        correctAnswer: "compound interest",
        question: "An interest calculated on the principal plus total amount of interest accumulated in previous periods.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["journal posting", "cost accounting", "general inventory", "ledger posting"],
        correctAnswer: "cost accounting",
        question: "The process of determining the actual cost of manufacturing a product or of rendering a service is.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["original capital", "working capital", "investment", "equity capital"],
        correctAnswer: "equity capital",
        question: "Funds for financing an engineering or business enterprise which is owned by the investors in the enterprise and they expect to earn profit from their investment, however, there is no obligation to pay them when there is no profit.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["hunter", "barter", "partial", "exchange"],
        correctAnswer: "barter",
        question: "The process of exchange where no single medium of exchange is used",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["all of these", "unliquidated damages", "late payments", "liquidated damages"],
        correctAnswer: "unliquidated damages",
        question: "Means sums such as jury would award when the case is presented to them upon its own merits.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["debt ratio", "price-earning ratio", "dividend yield", "equity ratio"],
        correctAnswer: "price-earning ratio",
        question: "The ratio of the market price per share to the earnings per share is",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["promotion cost", "development cost", "prime cost", "production cost"],
        correctAnswer: "prime cost",
        question: "The sum of all direct material costs and direct labor costs.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["individual ownership", "enterprise", "partnership", "corporation"],
        correctAnswer: "partnership",
        question: "An association of two or more persons for the purpose of engaging in a business for profit",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["grievance", "convict", "forced", "bias"],
        correctAnswer: "grievance",
        question: "This is a general term applied to an employee who feels he is or has suffered injustice",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["craft union", "association", "order center", "gang"],
        correctAnswer: "craft union",
        question: "This is an association of employees possessing a cmmon interest or skill or held together by employment in a single occupation or a group of closely related occupations",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["depletion", "depreciation", "deflation", "inflation"],
        correctAnswer: "inflation",
        question: "When prices go up in general, there is:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["license", "franchise", "monopoly", "goodwill"],
        correctAnswer: "franchise",
        question: "The exclusive right of a compnay to provide a specific product or service in a stated region of the country is",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Fixed assets", "Intangible assets", "Variable assets", "Liquid assets"],
        correctAnswer: "Liquid assets",
        question: "Assets which includes cash, accounts receivable within a short time or at least within the present accounting period, raw materials, goods in the process of prudction and finish goods ready for sale.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["savings", "check down", "checkoff", "tax fee"],
        correctAnswer: "checkoff",
        question: "Money which is remitted to the union is deducted from the employees wages by the employer for union dues or assessments",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["depletion", "normal depreciation", "physical depreciation", "functional depreciation"],
        correctAnswer: "physical depreciation",
        question: "The type of depreciation due to the lessening of the physical ability of a property to produce results",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["equity ratio", "debt ratio", "quick ratio", "benefit-cost ratio"],
        correctAnswer: "debt ratio",
        question: "THe ratio of total liabilities to total assets.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Royalty", "Disbursement", "Salary", "Commission"],
        correctAnswer: "Royalty",
        question: "An agreed payment made to an owner of an industrial property right for the grant of an exclusive sell for profit the item concerned.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["bonus pay", "call-in pay", "call-out pay", "extra pay"],
        correctAnswer: "call-in pay",
        question: "Where employees for work and are sent home without working a certain amount is paid to the employees.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["price discrimination", "price war", "oligopolistic monopoly", "price leadership"],
        correctAnswer: "price war",
        question: "A situation in which rival firms drive prices down through attempts to undercut each other&amp;amp;#39;s price is called:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["use value", "market value", "book value", "fair value"],
        correctAnswer: "book value",
        question: "The worth of the property as shown on the accounting records of an enterprise is",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["enterprise", "individual ownership", "corporation", "partnership"],
        correctAnswer: "individual ownership",
        question: "The simplest form of business organization, wherein a person uses his or her own capital to establish a business and is the sole owner.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["workers rally", "primary boycott", "none of these", "employers rally"],
        correctAnswer: "primary boycott",
        question: "Is one directed against an employer or company and consists of members of the union and their families withholding the patronage",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["uniform harmonic gradient", "uniform gemoteric gradient", "uniform arithmetic gradient", "uniform quadratic gradient"],
        correctAnswer: "uniform arithmetic gradient",
        question: "Economic analysis problems involve receipts or disbursements that increase or decrease by a uniform amount each period. This is known as",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["monopoly", "corporation", "competitors", "carter"],
        correctAnswer: "carter",
        question: "A formal organization of producers with an industry forming a perfect collision purposely formed to increase profit and block new comers from the industry:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["service-output method", "sum of the years digit method", "working hours method", "straight line method"],
        correctAnswer: "service-output method",
        question: "The method of depreciation which assumes that the total depreciation that has taken place is directly proportional to the quantity of output of the property up to that time",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["quick ratio", "debt ratio", "equity ratio", "current ratio"],
        correctAnswer: "current ratio",
        question: "The ratio of current assets to the current liabilities.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Coupon bonds", "Mortgage bonds", "Collateral trust bonds", "Debenture bonds"],
        correctAnswer: "Debenture bonds",
        question: "Those bonds without any security behind them except a promise to pay on a certain date by issuing corporation.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Law of demand", "Law of supply", "Law of diminishing return", "Law of supply and demand"],
        correctAnswer: "Law of supply and demand",
        question: "Under conditions of perfect competition the price at which a given product will be supplied and purchased is the price that will result in the supply and the demand being equal.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["value", "fixed assets", "present worth", "capital"],
        correctAnswer: "value",
        question: "The present worth of all future profits that are to be received through ownership of a particular property",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["diminished competition", "monopsony", "imperfect competition", "monopoly"],
        correctAnswer: "monopoly",
        question: "The opposite of perfect competition is",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["debt ratio", "current ratio", "quick ratio", "benefit-cost ratio"],
        correctAnswer: "benefit-cost ratio",
        question: "The ratio of the present value of all net benefits apart from the capital costs to those capital costs measured in money terms is known as",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["oligopoly", "oligopsony", "bilateral oligopoly", "bilateral oligopsony"],
        correctAnswer: "bilateral oligopoly",
        question: "A market situation where there are few sellers and few buyers.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["understanding", "back off", "mariana", "seniority"],
        correctAnswer: "seniority",
        question: "A system by which length of service is the decisive element in deciding on promotions or layoffs.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["bilateral monopsony", "monopsony", "bilateral monopoly", "monopoly"],
        correctAnswer: "bilateral monopoly",
        question: "A market situtation where there is one seller and one buyer.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["common stock", "capital stock", "incorporators stock", "preferred stock"],
        correctAnswer: "preferred stock",
        question: "It represent ownership and enjoys certain preferences than ordinary stock.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["use value", "utility value", "resale value", "scrap value"],
        correctAnswer: "scrap value",
        question: "The amount of property would sell for if disposed off as junk",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["sunk value", "discount", "depreciation", "profit"],
        correctAnswer: "discount",
        question: "THe difference between what a negotiable paper is worth in the future and its peresent worth is known as",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Monopolistic competition", "Perfect competition", "Oligopoly", "Perfect monopoly"],
        correctAnswer: "Monopolistic competition",
        question: "In this type of market, product of firms are differentiated by name, color, package, costumer service, credit conditions, etc, even if they are physically the same and its seller can raise the price to some degree iwthout losing his sales.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["extra money", "call-out pay", "excess pay", "featherbedding"],
        correctAnswer: "featherbedding",
        question: "A condition whereby payment is made for work not done or to the case where more workers are used than are a reasonable requirement for efficient operation.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["currency float", "currency depreciation", "currency appreciation", "currency devaluation"],
        correctAnswer: "currency depreciation",
        question: "The fall in the exchange rate of one currency in terms of others is called",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["total assets", "fixed assets", "current assets", "prepared assets"],
        correctAnswer: "current assets",
        question: "Liquid assets such as cash and other assets thta can be converted quickly into cash such as accounts receivable and merchandise are called",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["deferred annuity", "perpetuity", "delayed annuity", "simple annuity"],
        correctAnswer: "deferred annuity",
        question: "It is a series of equal payments occuring at equal intervals of time where the first payment is made after several periods after the beginning of the payment.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["pareto optimum", "maximim", "economic efficiency", "minimax"],
        correctAnswer: "pareto optimum",
        question: "A situation in which an events can increase the well being of one person without decreasing the well being of someone else is",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["capital", "ownership", "stock", "personal property"],
        correctAnswer: "ownership",
        question: "The equity of the person who normally posseses the asset is",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Law of diminishing profits", "Law of diminishing product", "Law of diminishing benefits", "Law of diminishing return"],
        correctAnswer: "Law of diminishing product",
        question: "According to this law &amp;amp;quot;If the input of one resource in the increased by equal increments per unit time while the inputs of other resources are held constant, total product of output will increase, but beyond some point, the resulting output increases will become smaller and smaller&amp;amp;quot;",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["uniform series compound amount factor", "single payment compound amount factor", "single payment present worth factor", "uniform series present worth factor"],
        correctAnswer: "single payment compound amount factor",
        question: "If F is the amount at the end of period and P is the principal at the beginning, then at an interest rate period of I, F = P(1 + i)&amp;amp;quot;. The quantity (1 + i)&amp;amp;quot; is called.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["check", "bond", "coupon", "note"],
        correctAnswer: "coupon",
        question: "A document that shows proof of legal ownership of a financial security",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Perpetuity", "Annuity due", "Deferred annuity", "Ordinary annuity"],
        correctAnswer: "Ordinary annuity",
        question: "A type of annuity where the payemts are made at the end of each payment period starting from the first period",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["unused value", "salvage value", "bargain value", "replacement value"],
        correctAnswer: "salvage value",
        question: "Scrap value of an asset is sometimes called",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["acknowledgement", "letter of debit", "check", "letter of credit"],
        correctAnswer: "letter of credit",
        question: "A letter of request whereby one person, usually a merchant or banker, requests some other person to advance money or to give credit up to a certain amount.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["book value", "utility", "market value", "fair value"],
        correctAnswer: "utility",
        question: "The value of the property where what the property  is worth to the owner as an operating unit.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["acid test ratio", "current", "debt ratio", "equity ratio"],
        correctAnswer: "acid test ratio",
        question: "Quick ratio is defined as the ratio of quick assets to the current liabilities, sometimes this is called",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Coupon bonds", "Mortgage bonds", "Collateral trust bonds", "Debenture bonds"],
        correctAnswer: "Collateral trust bonds",
        question: "Bonds secured by assets or bonds of one of the subsidiaries of the corporation.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["physical depreciation", "depletion", "functional depreciation", "normal depreciation"],
        correctAnswer: "depletion",
        question: "The decrease in the value of a property due to the gradual extraction its contents",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["present worth method", "future worth method", "rate of return method", "annual worth method"],
        correctAnswer: "annual worth method",
        question: "A basic methods or pattern for making economy studies in which the interest on the original investment (sometimes called minimum required profit) is included as a cost.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["monopsony", "oligopoly", "monopoly", "oligopsony"],
        correctAnswer: "monopsony",
        question: "A market whereby there is only one buyer of an itme for which there are no goods substitute.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["unamortized value", "scrap value", "sunk cost", "depreciation"],
        correctAnswer: "unamortized value",
        question: "The difference between the book value of an equipment and its resale when replaced",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["inventory", "both a &amp;amp;amp; b", "valuation", "appraisal"],
        correctAnswer: "both a &amp;amp;amp; b",
        question: "The process of determining the value of certain property for specific reasons",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Union agreement", "Union contract", "Union bargaining", "Union trade"],
        correctAnswer: "Union contract",
        question: "The negotiation of wage rates, conditions of employment, etc, by representatives of the labor force and management.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["variable cost", "marginal cost", "differential cost", "increment cost"],
        correctAnswer: "increment cost",
        question: "An increase in cost which is important in problems where it will be determiend whether an increase in production would be profitable for the enterprise.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["capitalized cost", "operating cost", "face value", "bond value"],
        correctAnswer: "capitalized cost",
        question: "THe sum of the first cost and the present worth all cost of replacement, operation and maintenance for a long time or forever",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["equity ratio", "quick ratio", "current ratio", "debt ratio"],
        correctAnswer: "equity ratio",
        question: "The ratio of total stockholders equity to the total assets is",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["equities", "assets", "values", "liabilities"],
        correctAnswer: "assets",
        question: "Anything of value possessedby an enterprise, which consists of properties and the right to the property, tangible or intangible which maybe used for the payment of debts.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["original cost", "equity capital", "ownership funds", "organization cost"],
        correctAnswer: "organization cost",
        question: "The amount of money spent in organizing a business and arranging for its financing and building.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["goodwill value", "differential value", "market value", "marginal revenue"],
        correctAnswer: "marginal revenue",
        question: "The amount received from the sale of an additional unit of a product.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Stock", "Intangible factors", "Tangible factors", "Equity"],
        correctAnswer: "Tangible factors",
        question: "Factors which can be expressed in monetary values.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["market value", "utility", "salvage value", "use value"],
        correctAnswer: "salvage value",
        question: "The price that can be obtained from the sale of the property after it has been used",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["maintenance of membership", "union rules and regulations", "membership agreement", "union law"],
        correctAnswer: "maintenance of membership",
        question: "This is a union security measure whereby a union employee pledges to remain a union member for the duration of collective bargaining agreement",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["bond", "cash flow", "check out", "money market"],
        correctAnswer: "cash flow",
        question: "The actual accounts passing into and out of the treasury of financial venture.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["depression", "inflation", "depletion", "obsolescence"],
        correctAnswer: "obsolescence",
        question: "A loss of value occasioned by new developments which place the older property at a competitive disadvantage:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["original cost", "working capital", "development cost", "promotion cost"],
        correctAnswer: "promotion cost",
        question: "The sum of all the expenses necessary to organize the business enterprise and its financing until the time actual construction is done for the enterprise.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["laibility entry", "debit entry", "assets entry", "credit entry"],
        correctAnswer: "credit entry",
        question: "THe entry in the book of account where the ownership is greater than the difference between assets and liabilities.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["franchise value", "going value", "book value", "goodwill value"],
        correctAnswer: "franchise value",
        question: "An intangible item of value arising from the exclusive right of a company to provide a specific product or service in a stated region of the country.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["exclusive shop", "closed shop", "union shop", "open shop"],
        correctAnswer: "closed shop",
        question: "Normally these are phrases indicating that plant has only union members as employees or one where the union is the recognized bargaining agency",
        topic: "NA"
    },
]